<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">theMovies</string>


    <!--Menu String Resources-->
    <string name="movies_menu" translatable="false">Movies</string>
    <string name="setting_menu" translatable="false">Setting</string>


    <!--

    TV Show Resource String

    -->
    <string name="flash_overview">After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of super speed,
        granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen guardian angel.
        Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to discover he is not the only
        \"meta-human\" who was created in the wake of the accelerator explosion — and not everyone is
        using their new powers for good. Barry partners with S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life
        to protect the innocent. For now, only a few close friends and associates know that Barry is
        literally the fastest man alive, but it won\'t be long before the world learns what Barry
        Allen has become…The Flash.</string>
    <string name="flash_date">October 7, 2014</string>


    <string name="oldman_overview">The true story of Forrest Tucker, from his audacious escape from San
        Quentin at the age of 70 to an unprecedented string of heists that confounded authorities and
        enchanted the public. Wrapped up in the pursuit are a detective, who becomes captivated with
        Forrest’s commitment to his craft, and a woman, who loves him in spite of his chosen profession.</string>
    <string name="oldman_date">August 31, 2018</string>
    <string name="oldman_runtime">1h 33m</string>

    <!--
    Movie Genres
    -->
    <string name="genres_comedy">Comedy</string>
    <string name="genres_romance">Romance</string>

    <!--
    Movie Items
    -->
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="network_res">Network</string>
    <string name="runtime_res">Runtime</string>
    <string name="status_res">Status</string>
    <string name="movie_status">Released</string>


    <string name="hello_love_goodbye_overview">A love story of Joy and Ethan, Filipino workers based in Hong Kong.
        Ethan, a bartender, is keen on romantically pursuing Joy, a domestic helper who is wholly dedicated to providing
        for her family.</string>
    <string name="hello_love_goodbye_date">August 8, 2019</string>
    <string name="hello_love_goodbye_runtime">1h 58m</string>
    <string name="tv_show_menu" translatable="false">Tv Show</string>
</resources>
